The Princess Sapphire
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Princess Knight,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Forty-Ninth Episode
Mr. X
The army of Union X marches
toward the border of Silverland.
Its soldiers advance
destroying everything:
mountains, forests, cities
They carry with them
formidable and powerful weapons.
The huge army of Union X
is just outside Silverland, now.
The only obstacle placed in its
path is Mephisto's mountain.
But they will raze it to the ground and then
they will attempt to invade Silverland.
General, sir!
General Ghana, sir, at your command!
I come from Headquarters!
I am relaying the order to you...
...to conquer
Mephisto's mountain..
...before the bulk
of the troops arrive! - Very well!
At your command, General!
On the march!
Shoot!
Attack! Move out
Why are they practicing
archery and the spear?
To prevent the army
of Union X from invading Silverland.
It is now not far
from our borders.
They must practice every day.
So there are bad people
even among human beings?
Unfortunately yes, Hecate. There aren't
many, fortunately, but they do exist.
But humans can love
others and be loved by them, right?
Yes, exactly, that's right.
Oh, then I envy
human beings!
Hecate, there's no reason why you
can't care for people.
I want to care for people!
To love!
Princess, it's time for
the War Council!
Unfortunately, duty calls
- Will we see each other again, Sapphire?
- Yes.
We'll see each other in the hawthorn
forest in a week.
All right.
Be careful!
The army of Union X..
...might pass
in front of the mountain where you live
Yes, but you be careful too!
Sapphire said that I could love
someone like humans do.
- Hecate!
- Mom! Dad!
Tell me:
what were you thinking about?
Well, I
Listen, Hecate, it's no use
telling me lies.
You know I can read your mind.
You're interested in
human beings, aren't you?
- Confess!
- No, mother!
Don't lie to me! Don't you know what a
terrible punishment would be inflicted...
...on a daughter of Mephisto if she
fell in love with a human being!
It is so! Perhaps you don't know
..the punishment of the Great
Devil. You tell her, darling.
What is this punishment
of the Great Devil like?
Listen carefully, Hecate.
The punishment that the
Great Devil inflicts is so terrible...
Did you understand, Hecate? You must
never be a bad daughter!
I understand, mom and dad.
Good! Well done! Now we can go
to the Witches' Conference.
- The Witches' Conference?!
- Yes, the Witches' Conference!
Wait a second, dear!
Hecate, take this amulet.
It will inform me immediately
if anything should happen to you.
Take care of the house
while we are away.
Be on your guard
against the evil humans!
Bye, mom! Dad!
General, it seems that
the Mephistos are moving away!
Good! We will destroy the mountain!
Prepare the weapons!
Hecate, you must always remember
that you are our daughter,
the daughter of Mephisto!
You would receive a terrible punishment
from the Great Devil...
..if you were to fall in love
with a human being.
Oh, mom! But I...
Good, we will destroy the mountain!
Prepare the weapons!
What is happening?
Forward, fire! We must raze
that mountain down there to the ground!
- Who is this?
- She's a little girl!
She must be the daughter of Mephisto!
- We have to kill her!
- Yes, let's burn her like a witch!
No, better to kill her with the sword!
- Help! Mommy! Daddy!
- Prepare to die, little girl!
Wait! What are you doing?
Leave her alone!
- General, she's the daughter of Mephisto!
- It's an order!
Yes sir, General Ghana!
- What shall we do with her, General?
- I'll handle it.
I'll be responsible for her.
Leave her to me, for the moment.
But we can't take her with us!
I'll have to consult with Mr. X.
Until then,
no one will touch her! Clear?
Come here! Let me see your arm!
But you're wounded! Bring
some disinfectant and a bandage!
We must treat
this wound immediately.
Prepare a horse for her! Immediately!
Now listen to me:
I have to take you to Mr. X,
so follow me and don't play any tricks.
Do you understand, little girl?
Alright.
May I know what your name is?
- Yes, you can! My name is Hecate.
- You have a nice voice.
- Hecate... It's a nice name.
- And what is your name?
Me?... My name is Ghana.
Are you ready? Let's go!
I can't wait to get back home.
I'm worried about
leaving Hecate alone.
You shouldn't worry.
Our daughter, by now,
is old enough.
But what happened to our
house?! It's been wiped out!
- Hecate!
- Someone must have kidnapped her!
Look! There are tracks of many
people who passed through here!
Let's follow them!
Look, soldiers!
And Hecate is with them!
I know what to do!
What the hell is that?!
- But it's the devil!
- Yes, it's Mephisto!
Mephisto has come
to take revenge on us!
Have you seen my power?
I'll teach you another lesson,
if you don't give me back my daughter!
What is it?
You devil of a Mephisto,
I'm glad to see you
Who are you?
I am Mr. X,
a human Mephisto!
I intend to build
an "Empire of Evil" on Earth,
- just like you!
- An evil empire?!
Exactly!
Let evil invade the world!
As a first step, we
will conquer Silverland!
What do you say, Mephisto?
Do you want to ally with me?
His project interests me. If it's
true, I would be inclined to help him.
Yes, it's interesting. We
could help you, but later!
Right! After you've returned our
daughter Hecate to us, safe and sound!
All right, I'll return her to
you, but on one condition!
- What condition?
- On the condition that you capture..
...the Princess of Silverland:
Sapphire!
Hello, little birds,
little inhabitants of the woods.
And how are you, friends? It's been a long
time since we saw each other, hasn't it?
You know, I came here because
today I have an appointment with Hecate.
Right here, in this forest.
What's happening? What...?
Sapphire! We must kidnap you
and take you to Lord X!
- Oh, no, I don't want to!
- You cannot resist!
What happened to me?
Ah, yes, I understand!
I was taken by Mephisto
and brought to the Union X camp.
Now I must think of how to escape
somehow!
If the Princess escaped,
we would be killed.
You've done a fine job, Mephisto!
Now that Sapphire
is in your hands,
Silverland almost is as well,
don't you think?
It's true. And I owe it to you!
Sapphire is here!
I must save her!
I believe that is the tent
where they are holding her prisoner.
Who is behind me? Oh, you!
Hecate, what are you doing here? You were
looking at Sapphire's tent, weren't you?
Help her, please! She's my
friend! Please, Ghana, save her!
I can't, Hecate! I'm sorry. I
am a soldier and I have orders.
Even if your boss
is an evil man?
Fine, Ghana! If you don't want
to help her, then I'll take care of it!
Hecate, what are you saying?
I'd like to stop you,
but I can't.
Hecate!
Stay here, I'll take care of it!
- Hecate!
- Shut up! Details later!
Hurry up, quick!
This way, Sapphire!
Alarm!
The prisoner is escaping!
- Stop!
- Catch them!
Damn! We have to do
something, or they'll catch us!
Fine!
I won't let you pass!
You'll have to kill me!
You're a traitor, General Ghana!
Death to the traitor!
Run, Hecate!
If we could reach
the Black Forest, we'd be safe!
I wonder if Ghana managed
to save himself...!
What?! Ghana let
Sapphire escape? Damn it!
What are you waiting for?
Get her now!
It's useless!
It's too late now.
At this point,
there's nothing left to do!
You can't catch her again!
Mr. X, with the prisoner
there was also Mephisto's daughter,
- who helped her escape.
- What is this I hear?!
She dared to do this?!
Mephisto, it seems that you
have corrupted Ghana!
You must take care of it!
What do you intend to do, Mephisto?
Alright, I have an idea!
Ghana will lead
us on their trail.
I will bring Sapphire back.
Promise not to hinder us!
We will take care of
settling the matter.
Alright, I promise. Take Ghana!
Remember: keep your word!
I wonder if Hecate and
Sapphire will come to his aid.
Don't worry! They are too
fond of him not to come.
You'll see that my plan will work.
Now I will let them
know that Ghana is here!
Hail Mephisto!
Rest assured, they will
both come running here.
- how kind-hearted they are!
- Why did you light that fire?
Look up there!
The fire is bright..
..and projects Ghana's image on
the smoke that rises into the sky.
Look! Look, Sapphire!
Up there! See? It's Ghana!
- What?!
- Ghana! Ghana!
Ghana, I'm sorry...!
They've caught you, Ghana!
Come on, Hecate! I think you really
like that young General, don't you?
- Do you think you love him?
- Yes, but...
If you love him, don't worry.
Didn't I already tell you that even
a devil can love a human being?
Let's go help him! It seems he's
on the other side of the mountain.
- Let's hurry!
- Yes.
There they are! These are
definitely Hecate and Sapphire!
Let's stay hidden! I'm eager
to see what Hecate will do.
Oh, Ghana! Ghana!
I'm here!
I'm coming, Ghana!
Hecate!
Have you regained consciousness, Ghana?
Stay away from here, Hecate!
It's a trap! Go away, quickly!
Don't be a fool, Ghana!
I'll help you!
Come on, Hecate!
Climb a little higher!
What are you doing,
Hecate? You are disobeying...
...to all the advice
that your mother and I give you?
- Mom! Dad!
- Get down from that tree right now!
- Don't make me angry!
- Well, what are you waiting for?
Yes, maybe..
it's better if you get down!
Get down, Hecate! Leave me alone!
Forget about me!
Ghana, I can't forget you!
Mom! Dad! No, I can't do it!
- What?!
- What?
I'm sorry, Mom and Dad!
I feel like I have to help him.
Hecate, don't do anything crazy!
Remember what awaits you..
...if you fall in love
with a human being!
Hecate, I made a promise
to Mr. X!
Get down right now! I order you!
If you made a deal with him,
remember...
..that he's the last person in the world
who will keep his word!
Look there!
It looks like the right moment!
Are you ready to attack?
Fire!
Damn it, he betrayed us
Hecate! We have to get Ghana down
as soon as possible!
- Yes!
- Hurry! Be careful!
- Hecate, are you alright?
- Yes! I'll free you in a moment!
Thank you! Thank you, Hecate!
What are you doing, Hecate!
Don't stay there! It's dangerous!
- Get down!
- The cannons keep firing!
They'll hit you! Get down!
Damn them! I must try
at all costs to stop them!
Great Devil, I appeal to you!
Come to my aid!
You've made a mistake this time, Mephisto!
If you go against X,
it means you want to side
with Hecate,
who loves a human being!
If instead you want to defeat X,
I'll have to punish you!
Do you understand?
So there's nothing left for you to do
but support X!
That's fine, Ghana,
but hurry up!
You've almost reached the ground.
Now we have to think about Hecate
I'm glad that you're okay!
Hecate! My daughter! My daughter!
Don't die, dear!
My love! My little darling!
Don't die, please!
Hecate!
Damn you! You'll pay
for what you've done!
My wrath is terrible, Mr. X!
Help! Help!
Quite a fine job, dear!
Now that you’re safe,
look at me too, Hecate!
Mama!
Hail Mephisto!
Waters, seethe and break loose!
Let’s flee! Help! Let’s run away! Help!
They were truly stupid!
Thus Mephisto and his
wife sacrificed their lives.
Let’s retreat for now!
Mephisto!
You and your wife have
broken the law of the Great Devil!
I will transform you respectively
into a mountain and into a lake!
You will never be able to be demons again!
Hecate!
You are guilty
of having loved a human being,
therefore I will punish you too!
You can no longer be a demon.
...and enjoy the privileges
of demons!
From now on
you will be a poor mortal!
Dad! Mom!
Hecate, your parents
have made the rainbow...
..to wish you happiness
In this way, they are telling you to enter
the world of human beings...
...and to live happily with Ghana.
- Ghana!
- Hecate!
Let's go, friends!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP